<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<article>
	<h1>Driving simulator 2021</h1>
	<p class="date">17.10.2021</p>
	<p class="content">This 2D endless runner is my first game. The current version was made in about 6 hours using Unity game engine and it features randomly generated surroundings and obstacles. Right now I'm working on the second version that'd include new features, such as sound. The game can be downloaded <a href="https://scheibenwischer.itch.io/driving-simulator-2021">here</a>.</p>
	<img src="https://i.ibb.co/j8mKLgn/driving-simulator-2021-screenshot.png" alt="driving-simulator-2021-screenshot" border="0">
</article>
<article>
	<h1>Gaussian elimination calculator</h1>
	<p class="date">01.10.2021</p>
	<p class="content">Written in C++ as a school assignment, this program can solve linear equations by performing Gaussian elimination on its coefficient matrix.</p>
	<img src="https://i.ibb.co/3yPWk2C/gaussian-elimination-calculator.png" alt="gaussian-elimination-calculator" border="0">
</article>
<article>
	<h1>Portfolio website</h1>
	<p class="date">ONGOING</p>
	<p class="content">My portfolio website is this site you're on right now - its purpose is to showcase my personal projects. It's hosted on GitHub pages - this means I can't use a database to store information. In order to make editing this site easier, I'm loading the project list from an .xml file. This project never really stops as I constantly find new ideas for improvement - right now I'm working on a better design using flexbox.</p>
</article>
<article>
	<h1>IMGCRY</h1>
	<p class="date">2020</p>
	<p class="content">After reading about <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Steganography">steganography</a> - the practice of concealing a message within another message - I knew I had to try it myself. This program can hide a text by splitting and storing it as the least significant bit of an images' pixel colour value.
	The chages are very miniscule and usually it's impossible to tell the old and new picture apart.</p>
</article>
<article>
	<h1>3D Ortographic projection</h1>
	<p class="date">2019</p>
	<p class="content">This program can draw and rotate any convex shape that consists of triangles. Written in pascal using graph library.</p>
	<img src="https://i.ibb.co/j4LksjH/simplex-spin.gif" alt="simplex-spin" border="0">
</article>
	
